<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Matthew Lawrence Klein - A Personal Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.matthewlawrencekle.in/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Matthew Lawrence Klein - A Personal Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 01:28:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://blog.matthewlawrencekle.in/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Roll Your Own (Ish)</title>
      <link>http://blog.matthewlawrencekle.in/posts/roll-your-own-ish/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 01:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.matthewlawrencekle.in/posts/roll-your-own-ish/</guid>
      <description>I can do less.. more! One of the greatest joys I&amp;rsquo;ve experienced since learning to program has been the newly gained ability to reimagine how I interact with technology. A lot of my interactions through an internet browser or phone app are rooted in routine and familiarity. Ever look at a friend&amp;rsquo;s phone home screen? It&amp;rsquo;s always unfamiliar and the worst. When I want to know how much a copy of StarFox for Super Nintendo is going for, I hit command + space in MacOS to bring up Spotlight, type &amp;lsquo;ebay&amp;rsquo;, hit enter to open Chrome and navigate to ebay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recursion at the Cat Circus</title>
      <link>http://blog.matthewlawrencekle.in/posts/recursion-at-the-cat-circus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 16:50:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.matthewlawrencekle.in/posts/recursion-at-the-cat-circus/</guid>
      <description>Some Background Recently at work I faced an interesting challenge while implementing a new feature. When users load up a new instance of our app, the app scans their input data and then generates a series of default values that are stored in a state object. Elements like height, color, order, and labeling are all pieces of state that can be updated, saved, imported, and exported. Users can also supply their own state data to be used in lieu of the defaults, and users can have any number of different states associated with each project.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
